{
    "subject": "Peter_IV_of_Aragon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Maria_of_Navarre",
    "human_readable": "Peter IV of Aragon is married to Maria of Navarre.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.949224054813385,
            "question": "Is Maria of Navarre related to Peter IV of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9322186708450317,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Peter IV of Aragon and Maria of Navarre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921039342880249,
            "question": "To whom was Peter IV of Aragon married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9174160361289978,
            "question": "Is Peter IV of Aragon married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903108835220337,
            "question": "Who is married to Maria of Navarre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8844205737113953,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Peter IV of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8806735277175903,
            "question": "Who is Maria of Navarre married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8197139501571655,
            "question": "Name one spouse of Peter IV of Aragon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7508756518363953,
            "question": "Was Peter IV of Aragon married to Eleanor of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38367095589637756,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter IV of Aragon is married to Maria of Navarre.",
            "html": "yago_28352_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Peter IV of Aragon married to Eleanor of Castile?",
            "html": "yago_28352_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one spouse of Peter IV of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_28352_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Maria of Navarre married to?",
            "html": "yago_28352_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28352_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis triple is supported by the documents. The document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28352/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt` mentions that Maria of Navarre was probably commissioned by Peter IV, the \"Ceremonious,\" King of Aragon, for his wife. This implies that they were married."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Peter IV of Aragon is married to Maria of Navarre.\" Specifically, the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28352/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt states that Maria of Navarre was Queen of Aragon from 1338 until her death as the first of four wives of Peter IV of Aragon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}